Political Study Club 095
People's Archive, MLK Library
Political Study Club Collection
1914-1968
People's Archive, MLK Library
Political Study Club of Washington, D.C.
095
0.25 Linear feet
1 Boxes
Arrangement
Processed without series.
Biographical / Historical
The Political Study Club of the District of Columbia was organized on October 13, 1899, by Helen Rand Tindall. The club was originally an afternoon suffrage club, but after the adoption of the 19th Amendment, the objective became "the study of the United States government in its home and foreign relations (non-partisan)."
Custodial History
This collection was removed from the vertical files.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of records pertaining to the Political Study Club of Washington, D.C. including yearbooks, annual breakfast programs, and clippings.
Yearbooks; Societies and clubs; Ephemera; Politics and government
- Series 1
  - Yearbooks (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Yearbooks, 1927-1928 (Item 1)
    - Yearbooks, 1935-1936 (Item 2)
    - Yearbooks, 1936-1937 (Item 3)
    - Yearbooks, 1939-1941 (Item 4)
    - Yearbooks, 1947-1948 (Item 5)
    - Yearbooks, 1949-1950 (Item 6)
  - Programs (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Annual Breakfast Programs, 1936 (Item 1)
    - Annual Breakfast Programs, 1937 (Item 2)
    - Annual Breakfast Programs, 1940 (Item 3)
    - Annual Breakfast Programs, 1941 (Item 4)
  - Clippings, 1914-1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)